(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
【 超重大告知あり‼ 】#鷹嶺ルイ生誕バンドLIVE 『L -challenger-』
[Major Announcement!!] #TakaneLuiBirthdayBandLIVE "L -challenger-"
鷹嶺ルイ生誕バンドライブ『L -challenger-』にお越しのみなさん、待ったかねー！
Everyone attending Takane Lui's Birthday Band Live "L -challenger-", did you wait long?
HoloXの女幹部、鷹嶺ルイと申します。
I am the female executive of HoloX, Takane Lui.
本日は待ちに待った生誕ライブ！
Today is the long-awaited birthday live!
開演に先立ちまして注意事項とお知らせです。
Before the show starts, here are some precautions and announcements.
このライブは全編無料、生バンドでお送りいたします。
This live will be a full-length free performance with a live band.
絶対に見逃せない超超超超重大発表もございますので、
There is also a super super super super important announcement that you absolutely cannot miss,
最後までぜひ見ていってくださいね。
so please be sure to watch until the very end.
感想はハッシュタグ、#鷹嶺ルイ生誕バンドライブ になっております。
For your impressions, use the hashtag #TakaneLuiBirthdayBandLive.
SNSでスクショ付きでガンガンポストして盛り上がってくれると嬉しいです。
I'd be happy if you could liven things up by posting lots of screenshots on SNS.
そして、本編終了後の21時15分からは、
And from 21:15 after the main performance,
メンバーシップ限定ライブもございます。
there will also be a membership-exclusive live.
メンバーシップライブももちろん生バンドで歌っちゃいますので、
Of course, I'll also be singing with a live band for the membership live,
この機会にメンバーシップへのご参加、お待ちしております。
so I'm looking forward to you joining the membership on this occasion.
さて、ここからがお知らせです。
Now, here are the announcements.
早く集まってくださったみなさんに、
To everyone who gathered early,
鷹嶺ルイ誕生日記念2024グッズ情報を先出ししたいと思います。
I'd like to pre-release information about the Takane Lui Birthday Celebration 2024 goods.
今回のグッズは4種類。
There are four types of goods this time.
最初はこちら。
First is this one.
ライブといえば、ビッグタオル！
Speaking of live shows, the Big Towel!
今回のライブテーマにぴったりなカッコよく歌う私を、
Kakege-papa drew a cool illustration of me singing,
かかげパパが描き下ろしてくれました。ありがとう！
perfectly matching the theme of this live. Thank you!
大きなタオルなので、イベントで背中からかければルイ推しをアピールできちゃいます。
It's a large towel, so if you drape it over your back at events, you can show off your support for Lui.
続いてはこちら。
Next is this one.
ランダム缶バッジ！
Random Tin Badge!
楽器を演奏する可愛いイラストが全4種類。
There are four types of cute illustrations of me playing instruments.
1種類がランダムで封入されております。
One type is included at random.
イラストはGurin.先生に描いていただきました。ありがとうございます！
The illustrations were drawn by Gurin-sensei. Thank you very much!
これはね、すごい可愛いので全種類集めたくなっちゃいますよね。
These are really cute, so you'll want to collect all the types, right?
続いてはこちら。
Next is this one.
おでかけルイぬいぐるみ！
Odekake Lui Plushie!
先日お披露目されたばかりの新衣装がぬいぐるみになって登場です。
My new costume, which was just revealed the other day, is now available as a plushie.
かなりリクエストが多かった持ち運びしやすいサイズ...
This is a portable size that many people requested...
サイズになっておりますので、
...so it's a size that
色んなところに連れて行っていただければなと思います。
you can take with you to various places.
最後はこちら。ボディ痛バ！
Last but not least, we have this: the Body Itabag!
今回のランダム缶バッジや、
This itabag is a perfect match for the
お出かけルイぬいぐるみとの相性もバッチリの痛バが登場です！
random pin badges and the "Odekake Lui" plushie!
私のモチーフがさりげなくあしらわれたデザインで、
The design features my motif subtly incorporated,
男女問わず使えるバッグになっております。
making it a bag that anyone can use regardless of gender.
ストラップ位置を変えることで
It's a 2-way bag that can also be used
ショルダーバッグにもなる2way仕様です！
as a shoulder bag by changing the strap position!
ぜひこれを持って、ルイ推しを全力アピールしてください！
Please get one and show off your support for Lui to the fullest!
ということで、こちらの4種類のグッズが全て入った
So, we also have a full set available that
フルセットもご用意しております。
includes all four types of goods.
フルセットには、箔押し複製サイン入り
The full set comes with a foil-stamped replica
チケット風特典カードと、特典ボイスがついております。
signed ticket-style bonus card and a bonus voice.
今回、直筆特典は数量限定バージョンで
This time, the handwritten bonus is available
ご用意させていただきました。
as a limited-quantity version.
今回はですね、直筆メッセージを心を込めて
For this one, I've put my heart into
入れさせていただきました。
writing handwritten messages.
数量限定ですが、いつもより多めに
Although it's a limited quantity,
用意させていただきましたので、
I've prepared more than usual,
一人でも多くの方に手に取ってもらえたら嬉しいです。
so I'd be happy if as many people as possible could get one.
特典ボイスは、ライブの後の打ち上げパーティーを
The bonus voice is a situation voice imagining
イメージしたシチュエーションボイスになっております。
an after-party following the live performance.
今回も私が台本を書かせていただきました。
I wrote the script for it this time as well.
こちらは通常も、限定バージョンにも
This bonus is included in both the
共通で入ってくる特典になっておりますので、
regular and limited versions,
ぜひ聞いていただけると嬉しいです。
so I'd be happy if you gave it a listen.
グッズはこのライブ本編終了後の21時から
Sales for the merchandise will start at 9:00 PM,
ホロライブプロダクションのオフィシャルショップで
after this live performance concludes, on the
販売開始になります。
Hololive Production Official Shop.
ライブを楽しんだ後はグッズもよろしくね！
Please check out the goods after enjoying the live!
お待たせしました。鷹嶺ルイ生誕バンドライブ
Thank you for waiting. Takane Lui's Birthday
『L -challenger-』まもなく開演です。
Band Live "L -challenger-" is about to begin.
この日のためにたくさん準備をしてきました。
I've done a lot of preparation for this day.
全力で歌うので最後までみんなで盛り上がっていきましょう。
I'm going to sing with all my might, so let's all have a blast together until the very end.
準備はいいか！
Are you ready?
それではいきましょう。まずはオープニングアクトです。
Here we go! First up is the opening act.
ボルテージを上げてくれるユニットといえば...
Speaking of the unit that'll crank up the voltage...
La la la...
迷宮なラビリンス
Meikyuu na Labyrinth
のまれかけた招待状
An invitation about to be swallowed
秘密の屋敷 迷宮マンション
A secret mansion, a maze apartment
ガタガタの戸 あの声に
At the rattling door, to that voice
No pain, no gain, okay
狙う獲物 ホークアイ
The prey I'm aiming for, Hawk Eye
迫る恐怖は ワークアイ
The approaching terror is Work Eye
放射状に 突破口を
Radially, a breakthrough
待つほどだろ 総まとめ
Just wait for it, the summary
エクスに取り込まれていくよ
I'm being swallowed by X
風真でござる！
It is Kazama!
不条理な見学ツアー
An irrational study tour
ドアからドアへ友情
Friendship from door to door
さあ かつごうやりよりビューワー
Come on, let's carry the viewers rather than spears
響け笑い声
Let our laughter resound
La la la...
詰まり本件
In short, this matter
思考こそパワー
Thought itself is power
素敵な迷宮のラビリンス
A wonderful maze, a labyrinth
並び立つシルエット
Standing side-by-side silhouettes
恐怖描写で 接続ワイファイ
Connecting Wi-Fi with horror descriptions
これマジで最強ルームだけど
This is seriously the best room, though
片窓の回廊をポツリ
Slightly in the corridor of a single window
危ないって Mansion
I told you it's dangerous, Mansion
One key
虚実踊れマリオネット
Dance through truth and falsehood, marionette
落ちる平原 何度もネット
The falling plains, the net again and again
ランク外は眼中ないが 何度くらいあかんくない？
Out of rank is out of sight, but how bad is it?
エクスに取り込まれてくくく
Swallowed by X, ku ku ku
迷える子羊くんたち
You wandering little lambs,
お砂糖マヨネーズそれとピンクのママいっぱいじゃハイになれるドリンクできたよー
I made a drink with sugar, mayo, and lots of Pink Mama to get you high!
ロックで飲んでくださいね、ホロックスだけに、はは！
Please drink it on the rocks! Just like holoX, haha!
さあさあ、皆の衆、飲んでいこうでござる！
Now, everyone, let's drink!
おいおい、減るの早っ！
Hey, it's disappearing fast!
いや、お前が飲むんかい！
Wait, you're the one drinking it?!
じゃあ、とりあえず... かんぱーい！
Then, for now... Cheers!
Bye bye!
鏡の回廊から
From the mirror corridor
低音 本性 警報
Low frequency, true nature, alarm
塗り替えられる宵夜
The evening night being repainted
響かせろ 笑い声
Let the laughter resound
お前たちも ララパパッパパ
Everyone too, la-la-pa-pa-ppa-pa
ララパパッパパ
La-la-pa-pa-ppa-pa
ララパパッパパ Yes!
La-la-pa-pa-ppa-pa Yes!
ララパパッパパ
La-la-pa-pa-ppa-pa
さあ集え 五人の元
Now gather, to the side of the five
肩を組んで 声を高らかに
Shoulder to shoulder, voices raised high
ラパパ ラララパパッパ
La-pa-pa la-la-la-pa-pa-ppa
エデンの海を越えるため
To cross the sea of Eden
つまり冒険 覆したい
In other words, an adventure I want to overturn
素敵な迷宮の スーパーフューチャーパーティー ラビリンス
A wonderful labyrinth's super future party labyrinth
バイホーラッス
Bye-holas
TAKANE LUI 3D LIVE
2024.06.11
猫又おかゆ NEKOMATA OKAYU
Nekomata Okayu
森カリオペ MORI CALLIOPE
Mori Calliope
宝鐘マリン HOUSHOU MARINE
Houshou Marine
常闇トワ TOKOYAMI TOWA
Tokoyami Towa
ラプラス・ダークネス LA+ DARKNESSS
La+ Darknesss
博衣こより HAKUI KOYORI
Hakui Koyori
沙花叉クロヱ SAKAMATA CHLOE
Sakamata Chloe
風真いろは KAZAMA IROHA
Kazama Iroha
鷹嶺ルイ TAKANE LUI
Takane Lui
L-challenger-
Welcome, Lui's Birthday Party!
今日は楽しんでいこう！
Let's have fun today!
生バンドです！
It's a live band!
1曲目はオリジナル曲、
The first song is an original song,
新しいオリジナル曲です。
it's a new original song.
「Tori To Re:TreaT」聴いてください！
Please listen to "Tori To Re:TreaT"!
鳥籠にフリクション
Friction in the birdcage
かきあげて 私の世界
Stirring up my world
開幕して 無限リスタートで
Opening with an infinite restart
点君は 此処の虜
And you are a prisoner here
ティティティ リッター ティティティ リッター
Ti-ti-ti re-treat, ti-ti-ti re-treat
爪を隠して
Hiding the claws
誘ってあげる
I'll invite you
ルイは友を呼ぶ
Lui calls her friends
Welcome to my Little World
トリ トリ トリ ようこそ虜に待っててね
Tori, tori, tori, welcome, my prisoner, please wait
世界を虜に満たして
Fill the world with prisoners
トリ トリ トリ 虜に虜中注意
Tori, tori, tori, beware of being captivated
数え切れてるの？
Can you count them?
まいかむかむ 私の世界へ
My come-come to my world
解き放つの カデンツァ
Releasing the cadenza
最期に音奏でて放て 虜に
Finally play the sound and release, into captivity
鳥 頂上の鳥が手
Tori, the bird at the peak is in hand
曖昧 ミールイラヴ 友は友
I, my, me... Lui-love, friends are friends
友
Friends
揺れる篭のペンデュラム
The swinging pendulum of the cage
鵜の目鷹の目 空回る
Looking with sharp eyes, spinning in vain
暗転状態 正常以上
Blacked-out state, more than normal
待て 君は篭の虜
Wait, you are the prisoner of the cage
歪な秘密
A distorted secret
話してあげる
I'll tell you
飛ぶ鳥にも落ちて
Even the flying birds fall
Welcome to my little ward, trip to
トリ・トリ・トリップ ようこそトリマネ
Tri-Tri-Trip, welcome to the bird cage
全界が虜で見つめる
The whole world gazes as prisoners
トリ・トリ・トリップ 陶酔に御注意
Tri-Tri-Trip, beware of the intoxication
振り出しの Welcome my world
Starting from the beginning, Welcome my world
トリ・トリ・トリップ ようこそトリマネ
Tri-Tri-Trip, welcome to the bird cage
全界は虜で見たして
Fill the whole world with prisoners
トリ・トリ・トリップ ありえないほど愛を
Tri-Tri-Trip, an impossible amount of love
揺らしてで Welcome 私の世界へ
Shake it, Welcome to my world
的外れガイダンス さしずめ重なる
Off-target guidance, eventually overlapping
離して
Release me
狂喜 容易な檻まで
To the cage where joy is easy
全界をずっと虜にするから
Because I'll make the whole world prisoners forever
この歌のラスト コンセントリ・カザルノト
The last of this song, concentric, the point of no-return
（トリ！）
(Tori!)
続いては！
Next up!
彼女を呼びたいと思います！
I'd like to call her out!
Hey, hey, everybody! What's up!
一緒に歌いましょう！
Let's sing together!
Let's rock!
もういいじゃん ムキになっちゃって 格好つけて
Give it a rest, getting all worked up and acting cool
格好良くない そういうの嫌いになってんだ
It's not cool, I'm starting to hate that kind of thing
放っておいてよ 知りたくない
Leave me alone, I don't want to know
もういいじゃん 焼けになっちゃって 嫉妬したり
Give it a rest, getting all desperate and jealous
じっとできない 聞こえないフリ
Can't stay still, pretending not to hear
うるせーばか 言ってくれるじゃん しんどいな
Shut up, you dummy, you really said it, it's exhausting
僕をまだ誰も覗かないよ
No one peeks at me yet
だから僕のことそっとしておいて
So leave me be
うるせーばか 間に合え ハイ ハイ ハイ
Shut up, you dummy, catch up, hi hi hi
受ける またのご指名 待ってるね
Okay, I'll take it, waiting for your next request
だとか本当は怯えてる吠える
Or something, actually being scared and howling
どうしたったー
What happened?
痛いくせに耐えてハイ ハイ ハイ
Even though it hurts, you endure it, hi hi hi
いつも平気なフリ ばかなの？
Always pretending to be fine, are you an idiot?
僕は壁を貼ったまま笑う
I smile with a wall built up
それ以上近づかないで
Don't get any closer than that
ででで 怖いじゃん ばかばっか
Because it's scary, you dummy, so many dummies
もういいじゃん まだ怒ってるの
Give it a rest, are you still angry?
放っておいてよ 放っておけない
Leave me alone, I can't leave you alone
見ないように 目をそらしたって
Even if you look away so as not to see
ついてくるじゃん やっぱり
You're following me after all
困ったら急にベイビーちゃん
Suddenly becoming a baby when in trouble
失ったら叫ぶベイビーちゃん
A baby who screams when they lose something
いや いや いや いや それで良くない
No, no, no, no, that's not good
僕は誰も覗かないよ
I don't peek at anyone
だだから僕のことそっとしておいて
So leave me be
嫌なこと全部大丈夫だと
If only I could say everything bad is okay
言えたらいいのにな
If only I could say that
思えたらいいのにな
If only I could think that
誓うよだったらね ねえ大正解
I swear, if that's the case, hey, the big correct answer
スロー僕はその通りなの待て
Slow, I'm just as you said, wait
言いたいこと殺したから
Because I killed what I wanted to say
もう忘れてくれ
Just forget about it now
うるせーばか 間に合え ハイ ハイ ハイ
Shut up, you dummy, catch up, hi hi hi
受ける またのご指名 待ってるね
Okay, I'll take it, waiting for your next request
だとか本当は怯えてる吠える
Or something, actually being scared and howling
痛いくせに耐えてハイ ハイ ハイ
Even though it hurts, you endure it, hi hi hi
いつも平気なフリ ばかなの？
Always pretending to be fine, are you an idiot?
僕は壁を貼ったまま笑う
I smile with a wall built up
本当ばかばっか いい加減ばか
Really so many dummies, just dummies
とんだバグばっか 出せなくて
Just terrible bugs, can't put them out
そんなことばっか思う僕もやっぱ
I guess I, who only thinks about things like that
どうしようもないんだ ばってん状態
Am hopeless, in a crossed-out state
期待の底耐えてらんないない
Can't stand the bottom of expectations
死ねるって僕もガチばかだね
Thinking I could die, I'm a real dummy too
今日も壁を貼ったまま笑う
Today too, I smile with a wall built up
それ以上近づかないで 怖いじゃん
Don't get any closer than that, it's scary
ばかばっか
So many dummies
ということで、改めて！
So, once again!
ちょっと喉がやばい...
My throat is a bit...
カリです！
It's Calli!
膝もやばい！大丈夫！
My knees are shot too! It's okay!
大丈夫です！問題ないです！
I'm fine! No problem!
ということで、ちょっと水飲んできていいですか？
So, can I go get some water?
そうですね、飲みたいと思う。
Yeah, I want to drink too.
じゃあカリに自己紹介をしててもらってもいいですか？
Then Calli, could you introduce yourself?
OKです！任せて！
OK! Leave it to me!
お願いします！
Please!
あー、皆さん！
Ah, everyone!
いつも頑張ってる死神、森カリオペですよね！
I'm the hard-working reaper, Mori Calliope, right!
ホロライブEnglish -Myth- の死神ですです！
I'm the reaper of Hololive English -Myth-!
破滅はここですです！
Destruction is right here!
Hey, everyone!
Thank you for watching!
ひゃー、楽し...ごめんごめんごめん！ごめん！
Hyaa, fun... sorry sorry sorry! Sorry!
楽しすぎる！
This is too much fun!
いやー、今日は来てくれてありがとうございます。
Man, thank you so much for coming today.
いえいえ、こちらこそ誘ってくれてありがとうございました！
No no, thank YOU for inviting me!
本当ね、「ばかばっか」...
Truly, 'Baka Bakka'...
歌いたかったんで...
I really wanted to sing this...
そうだね。すごい好きな曲。なんか...
Right. I really love this song. To be honest...
めちゃめちゃ緊張してた。実は。
I was actually really nervous.
あら。でもめっちゃかっこよかったです。
Oh? But you were really cool.
そうだね。そして、なんか...
Yeah. And also...
バンドもいるよね。
we have a band, too.
そう！
Yes!
すごい！わー！本当にびっくりした！
Amazing! Wow! I was really surprised!
生バンドでね、お送りしております。
We're performing with a live band.
かっこいい！
Cool!
めちゃめちゃかっこいい。
It's so cool.
これからもちょっと生バンドでお送りしたいと思いますので。
We'll continue with the live band for a bit.
ハッシュタグ #鷹嶺ルイ生誕バンドLIVE でたくさん呟いてくださると嬉しいです。
I'd be happy if you used the hashtag #鷹嶺ルイ生誕バンドLIVE to tweet a lot.
使って使って！
Use it, use it!
はい、今トレンド4位みたいなので。
Yes, it seems we're trending 4th right now.
うわぁ！
Wow!
お！
Oh!
1位まで押し上げてくれ！
Push us up to 1st!
お願いします！
Please!
頑張れみんな、お願い！
Good luck everyone, please!
ということで、カリが出てきたということは、ここから実はゲストパートになるので。
So, Calli's appearance means it's actually time for the guest part.
収録もしてあるんですけど、バンドの...
The band part is recorded, but...
これもね、バンドなんで、ぜひゲストパートをこれから3曲続けて見ていただければなと思います。
This is also with a band, so please enjoy the next three guest songs.
その間に喉を休めてきます。
In the meantime, I'll go rest my throat.
ということで、カリ、ありがとう！
So, Calli, thank you!
いえいえ、こちらこそ、楽しかった！
No, thank you, I had fun too!
じゃあ一緒にパート、ちょっと振ってもらってもいいですか？
Then, could you help me introduce the next part?
オッケーです！
Sure thing!
ということで！
So!
うん！
Yeah!
ゲストパートに...
To the guest part...
どうぞ！スタート！
Please! Start!
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
ホロホーク
作詞・作曲・編曲：まろん (IOSYS)
Holo Hawk
Lyrics, Comp, Arr: Maron (IOSYS)
単純で明快で簡単じゃない
It's not simple, clear, or easy
まだ騒騒と妄想と偏見でファイ
Still fighting with noise, delusions, and prejudice
それ完全な万全な設定じゃない
That's not a perfect setup
見逃してくれないか
Won't you look the other way?
体験と内面と空想のピッチ
The pitch of experience, inner thoughts, and fantasy
この繊細さ敏感さ共有しよう
Let's share this delicacy and sensitivity
ほら冷静な表情は実際チョーハイ
Look, a calm expression is actually super high
見つけてくれないか
Won't you find me?
ハイハイお姉さんしちゃってゴー
High high, playing the big sister, let's go
ハイハイ期待感背負っちゃってコー
High high, carrying expectations, go
ハイハイお姉さんしちゃってゴー
High high, playing the big sister, let's go
ハイハイ期待感背負っちゃってコー
High high, carrying expectations, go
ホロホロホクホロホクだけど
Holo holo hawk holo hawk, but...
高嶺の花みたいに扱っちゃいや
...don't treat me like an unattainable goal.
あのね誰もかれも私と勘違い
You see, everyone's mistaken about me
驚きの愛
A surprising love
ホロホロホクホロホクだけど
Holo holo hawk holo hawk, but...
ポンコツみがちょいあるだけで親近感
...a bit of clumsiness makes me relatable.
その才その最その際受け止めてよね
Accept that talent, that peak, that moment
高嶺の未来 乾杯
Cheers to the high-peak future!
しっかりウォッチ
Watch closely
アイマイユーノー
I-M-U-No
辛いとか苦手
I'm not good with spicy food
巻抜きでネ
Without the roll, please
イケメン降臨
A handsome man descends
意外とギャップ系
An unexpected gap
イメージ大変身
A major image change
オッケー！
Okay!
短縮の感性で内緒じゃない
My shortened sensitivity isn't a secret
合心配で相談ね散々でも
Concerned about consulting, even if it's terrible
狂騒のイヤボロの配信じゃない
It's not a noisy, low-quality stream
個人的限界開戦界
Personal limits in the opening battle world
ホロホロホクホロホクだけど
Holo holo hawk holo hawk, but...
少食のイサイだから怖がっちゃいや
...don't be afraid because I'm a small eater.
ほらね爪も羽もおしゃれに説いて
See, I explain my claws and feathers stylishly
隠しちょいない
Not hiding them at all
ホロホロホクホロホクだけど
Holo holo hawk holo hawk, but...
観察眼がちょいあるだけで緊張感
...a bit of observation makes things tense.
その才その最その際受け止めてよね
Accept that talent, that peak, that moment
高まる時代 乾杯
Cheers to the rising era!
ハイハイお姉さんしちゃってゴー
High high, playing the big sister, let's go
ハイハイ期待感背負っちゃってコー
High high, carrying expectations, go
ハイハイお姉さんしちゃってゴー
High high, playing the big sister, let's go
ハイハイ期待感背負っちゃってコー
High high, carrying expectations, go
ホロホロホクホロホクだけど
Holo holo hawk holo hawk, but...
高嶺の花みたいに扱っちゃいや
...don't treat me like an unattainable goal.
あのね誰もかれも私と勘違い
You see, everyone's mistaken about me
驚きの愛
A surprising love
ホロホロホクホロホクだけど
Holo holo hawk holo hawk, but...
ポンコツみがちょいあるだけで親近感
...a bit of clumsiness makes me relatable.
その才その最その際受け止めてよね
Accept that talent, that peak, that moment
高嶺の未来 乾杯
Cheers to the high-peak future!
愛じゃ高まる時代 乾杯
I said, cheers to the rising era with love!
オーバーバード
作詞・作曲・編曲：柊キライ
Overbird
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Hiiragi Kirai
四六時中 お帰りの会で 面倒くささを押し付けられてる 何から何まで
All day long, at the "welcome home" meeting, I'm forced to deal with bothersome things, from top to bottom.
お仕事はやめて まとめ役なら 聞く耳持たず頷きあってる 仲良しこよしで
Stop the work, if you're the mediator, just nodding along without listening, acting like best buddies.
さぁ だだだだ まれだまれだまれ あえよ 言えないね そんな強い言葉は
Now, da-da-da-da, shut up, shut up, shut up, let's meet, I can't say such harsh words.
少しだけ 静かにしてほしいね あぁ 私たち 大望へ
I want it to be a little quiet, ah, we're heading towards our great ambition.
世界 ゼンゼン ブクヤヤヤ 果てぬその日まで
The world is totally buku ya ya ya, until that day that never ends.
ベルレレ ブクヤヤヤ あなたの周りも ヨヨヨ
Berurere buku ya ya ya, everyone around you too, yo yo yo.
世界 ゼンゼン ブクアレアレ 約束の地まで
The world is totally buku are are, until the promised land.
サダダクヨ バッテンバッテン テンテン ブクヤヤヤ
Sadadakuyo batten batten, ten ten buku ya ya ya.
今日も期待 そっちのけだね 嫌になるから 私一人でも
Ignoring expectations again today, because I'm getting fed up, even if I'm alone...
やってのけますね 全て 全て 全て 捲って それを刺させてよ 大事なことなの 分かっているでしょう
I'll pull it off, turn everything over and let me strike it, it's important, you know that, right?
四六時中 お帰りの会で 面倒くさいまま 今日も明日も過ぎてゆくのでしょう
All day long, at the "welcome home" meeting, today and tomorrow will probably pass by while still being a bother.
たぶんね 目をあけましょう 時計の中 忘れたこと 忘れてた
Probably, let's open our eyes, I forgot what I forgot inside the clock.
さぁ だだだだ まれだまれだまれ あえよ 言えないね そんな強い言葉は
Now, da-da-da-da, shut up, shut up, shut up, let's meet, I can't say such harsh words.
少しだけ 静かにしてほしいね あぁ 私たち 大望へ
I want it to be a little quiet, ah, we're heading towards our great ambition.
今と未来 見たかったはずなのに
Even though we were supposed to want to see the present and future...
世界 ゼンゼン ブクヤヤヤ 見えぬその日まで
The world is totally buku ya ya ya, until that day we can't see.
ドドドド ブクヤヤヤ 混むの理（ことわり） ヨヨヨ
Do-do-do-do buku ya ya ya, the logic of crowding, yo yo yo.
今は ゼンゼン ブクサササ あなたも同じなら
Right now, totally buku sa sa sa, if you're the same too.
叩き震わば バッテンバッテン
If we strike and tremble, X X.
世界 ゼンゼン ブクヤヤヤ 果てぬその日まで
The world is totally buku ya ya ya, until that day that never ends.
ベルレレ ブクヤヤヤ あなたの周りも ヨヨヨ
Berurere buku ya ya ya, everyone around you too, yo yo yo.
世界 ゼンゼン ブクアレアレ 約束の地まで
The world is totally buku are are, until the promised land.
さぁ 叩き震わば バッテンバッテン テンテン ブクしたいなら ベンゼンワインを開けましょう
Now, if we strike and tremble, X X, ten ten, if you want to buku, let's open the Benzene wine.
誰かに言われなくたって 私のほうがもっと嫌いだ
Even if nobody tells me, I hate myself even more.
FIRST CRY
作詞・作曲・編曲：堀江晶太
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Horie Shouta
うるさいな 騒がしい 視界を塞いで 理不尽な理由を書き連ねる 虚実にずっと居残り
It's noisy, so loud, blocking my view, listing unreasonable reasons, staying in falsehood and truth forever.
窓の向こうに黒い影があって 何も言わずにこちらを見ていた
There's a black shadow beyond the window, looking here without saying anything.
私はあなたに救われたくて鳴くんじゃない 産声は止められないもの
I'm not crying out because I want to be saved by you, the first cry is something that can't be stopped.
何千回と間違いに しみつく細胞 希望と絶望の夜中を纏って
Staining cells with thousands of mistakes, wearing the midnight of hope and despair.
鈍い光を許したいのは 他ならない私だった
The one who wanted to forgive the dull light was none other than me.
息をして 目を開けて
Breathe, open your eyes.
これが最後かどうか 知るすべはないよ 知りたくもないよ
Whether this is the last or not, there's no way to know, and I don't want to know.
優しいな...
How gentle...
混濁と闇を揺らそうか
Shall we shake the turbidity and darkness?
解けない答えを塗りつぶした
Painted over the unsolvable answers.
どうせ真っ白くもないよと
Saying it's not pure white anyway.
惑わされてくすぐに越えて
Being led astray, cross it immediately.
それは祈るような啜り泣きだって
Even if it's a prayer-like sob.
私はあなたを救える言葉を知らないけど
I don't know the words that can save you, but...
寂しいねって声をかけた
I said, "It's lonely, isn't it?"
何千回ともう一度死に損なおう
Let's fail to die once more, thousands of times.
希望と絶望の様な顔を纏って
Wearing a face like hope and despair.
何千回ともう一度息を食らえ
Swallow your breath once more, thousands of times.
私も続くよ 窓の向こう側へ
I'll follow too, to the other side of the window.
醜い光を愛せた時
When we can love the ugly light.
終わらせたかった産声を
The first cry we wanted to end.
歌にしよう
Let's turn it into a song.
リッパーのこの刃面に
On this blade face of the ripper.
泥をつけて這っていた
Crawling with mud on it.
CHARISMA
作詞・作曲・編曲：jon-YAKITORY
Lyrics, Music, Arrangement: jon-YAKITORY
鳴らせ 研いだ爪立てて
Make it ring, with sharpened claws.
信じられるものは自分だけだと
Convinced that I was the only one I could believe in.
思い込んで進み続けた
I kept moving forward.
あの子みたいにすれば
If I do it like that girl...
君じゃそれは無理だ
“It's impossible for you.”
言わせておけばいいさ
Just let them say what they want.
たった一人 逆境の先
All alone, beyond the adversity.
あいつらから奪い去れ
Snatch it away from them.
私の邪魔させやしない
I won't let them get in my way.
雷火の影 見据えた髪
Hair that gazed at the shadow of the lightning fire.
荒野の果てから空へと
From the end of the wasteland to the sky.
飛んで行く私を見ないなんて Bad boy
Not looking at me as I fly away, what a bad boy.
失敗は止まった時
Failure is when you stop.
今日も挑み張っている
Today too, I'm challenging and holding on.
意味のないものはないと
Thinking there's nothing without meaning.
信じられるものを
Until I find something...
見つけ出すまで
...I can believe in...
泥に足掻いて笑い飛ばした
...I struggled in the mud and laughed it off.
あの子はもう終わりだ
“That girl is finished.”
これ以上はないな
“There's nothing more than this.”
言わせておけばいいさ
Just let them say what they want.
いつか光が灯り冷めても
Even if the light turns on and cools down someday.
夢見ていた大喝采
The great applause I was dreaming of.
私はここで死にたくねえ
I don't want to die here.
一生の旅 逆境の先
A lifelong journey, beyond the adversity.
あいつらから奪い去れ
Snatch it away from them.
私の邪魔させやしない
I won't let them get in my way.
雷火の影 見据えた髪
Hair that gazed at the shadow of the lightning fire.
荒野の果てから空へと
From the end of the wasteland to the sky.
飛んで行く私を見ないなんて Bad boy
Not looking at me as I fly away, what a bad boy.
Bad boy
はい、ということで3曲ゲストパートをお届けして、
All right, so we've presented three guest tracks,
先ほど『CHARISMA』というジョンやきとりさんから書き下ろしていただいた楽曲を歌わせていただきました。
and just now I sang 'CHARISMA,' a song written for me by jon-YAKITORY.
いかがだったでしょうかー！
How did you like it?!
イェーイ！イェーイ！
Yay! Yay!
ということで、ちょっとね、喉も回復したので
So, since my throat has recovered...
歌えてよかったなと思いますけれども
I'm glad I could sing.
あ、トレンドが１位になったそうで、みんなありがとう！
Oh, it seems we hit #1 on trending! Thank you everyone!
たくさん呟いてくれて、あ、ポストしてくれてたね
For tweeting so much—oh, you were posting, right?
ポストしてくれてありがとう！
Thank you for posting!
まだまだ、たくさんポストしてくれると嬉しいです
I'd be happy if you keep posting more.
ハッシュタグ #鷹嶺ルイ生誕バンドライブ です。みんなありがとう！
The hashtag is #TakaneLuiBirthdayBandLive. Thank you everyone!
いや今回はね、あの、もうすでにリリースされている楽曲に関しては
This time, regarding the songs that have already been released...
カリ先輩と、そしてマリン先輩、おかゆ先輩、そしてトワ様と一緒に歌わせていただいたんですけど
I sang them with Calli-senpai, Marine-senpai, Okayu-senpai, and Towa-sama.
まったく違った感じになってて、私も楽しかったなと思うんですけど
They had a completely different vibe, and I had a lot of fun too.
皆さんいかがだったでしょうか？
How did you all like it?
いかがだったかな？
How was it?
おめでとう、おめでとう、ありがとう、ありがとう、みんなありがとう。楽しかったかな？
Congrats, congrats! Thank you, thank you, thank you everyone. Did you enjoy it?
あ、「HoloHawk」がめちゃくちゃ良かった！って言ってる海外ニキおりますね。ありがとう！
Oh, I see some overseas fans saying "HoloHawk was amazing!" Thank you!
はい、なんか、あの、コメントがすごい勢いで流れているので固まってしまいました。ありがとう！
Yes, well, the comments are flowing so fast that it froze. Thank you!
ということで、これからね、あの、２曲歌わせていただくんですけど
So, I'm going to sing two songs now.
２曲で、あの、本編は終了
And with these two songs, the main show ends...
嘘です。あの、２曲以降もあるんですけど
Just kidding! There's more after these two.
一応２曲ね、これから続けて歌わせていただきます
But for now, I'll sing two more songs back-to-back.
次に歌う曲なんですけれども、FAKE TYPE.さんに書き下ろしていただいた楽曲をやらせていただきます
The next song is one written specifically for me by FAKE TYPE.
「ひみつの おしごと」という楽曲なんですけれども
It's a song called "Himitsu no Oshigoto" (Secret Work).
めちゃくちゃかっこいい曲になっているので、ぜひ、ちょっと楽しんで聴いていただければなと思います
It's a really cool song, so I hope you enjoy listening to it.
その前に、ちょっと水を飲んでもいいですか？
Before that, can I drink some water?
いいよ、ということで水を飲みまーす
Sure! So, I'm drinking water.
よし、歌える。俺なら行ける
Okay, I can sing. I can do this.
行けるよね？ みんな行けるよね？
I can do it, right? Everyone, I can do it, right?
ということで、これから歌わせていただく曲は FAKE TYPE.さんに書き下ろしていただいた曲...
So, the song I'm about to sing is written for me by FAKE TYPE...
楽曲、もうボロボロだ。楽曲「ひみつの おしごと」です。ぜひ聴いてください
Song—I'm stumbling. The song "Himitsu no Oshigoto". Please listen.
引けないなんて言えない
I can't say I won't back down
後に引けない
No backing out now
ひみつの おしごと
作詞：TOPHAMHAT-KYO (FAKE TYPE.) 作曲：FAKE TYPE. 編曲：DYES IWASAKI (FAKE TYPE.)
Himitsu no Oshigoto
Lyrics: TOPHAMHAT-KYO (FAKE TYPE.) / Music: FAKE TYPE. / Arrangement: DYES IWASAKI (FAKE TYPE.)
無闇に火花重ねない Fry-hi-ya
Don't let sparks fly aimlessly, Fry-hi-ya
いざもっと挑戦のハラハラ
The usual thrill of a challenge
火花散らせば命から
With sparks flying, my life is on the line
待ったなし小気味ダンス
No waiting, lively dance
しなやかなステップでかわしちゃうぜ
Dodge them all with supple steps
サラリーの社会が眠る頃に
When the working world is asleep
ハラリな輩爆睡する頃に
When the noisy bunch is fast asleep
落ち着きもっと冷静標的前を潜り抜けて
Calmly and coolly slipping through before the target
平日はシュビドゥビドゥ
Weekdays, shoobie doobie doo
週末もシュビドゥビドゥ
Weekends too, shoobie doobie doo
時にキツくハードに
Sometimes tough and hard
時に平和だバーディー
Sometimes peaceful, birdie
今宵ひみつのおしごと
Tonight, a secret work
Here we go! 今夜だってバンバンバン
Here we go! Tonight too, bang bang bang
外さないクリア
A clear shot, no misses
It’s the show! 狙い合ってラッキー笑顔
It’s the show! Aiming for lucky smiles
今はなになり憂いを見ない
Seeing no constraints now
Here we go! 攻め合ってバンバンバン
Here we go! Attacking each other, bang bang bang
悟られずカバー
Covering up without being noticed
Here we go! 気取っちゃってさあ出番
Here we go! Putting on airs, it's showtime
後腐れなく
No lingering attachments
決して逃さない
Won't let you get away
向いた牙を抜くまでは
Until I pull those bared fangs
決して汚さない
Will never let it get dirty
守る脱獄の看板
Protecting the sign of the jailbreak
人知れない根回し
Secretly pulling strings
Oh yeah, お見舞いするあとの祭り
Oh yeah, giving you a lesson after it's too late
Oh yeah, 響く昼の音がお仕置きの合図
Oh yeah, the midday echo is the signal for punishment
誰も彼もチェック、もっとアゲ！
Checking everyone, get even more hyped!
平日からシュビドゥビドゥ
From weekdays, shoobie doobie doo
年末もシュビドゥビドゥ
Year-end too, shoobie doobie doo
お任せあれハントリー
Leave it to me, hunt-ly
表立って唐突に
Suddenly appearing in the open
もとい秘密のおしごと
Again, a secret work
Here we go! 今夜だってバンバンバン
Here we go! Tonight too, bang bang bang
外さないクリア
A clear shot, no misses
It’s the show! 狙い合ってラッキー笑顔
It’s the show! Aiming for lucky smiles
しばしばルイは友を呼ぶ
Often Lui calls friends
Here we go! 攻め合ってバンバンバン
Here we go! Attacking each other, bang bang bang
悟られずカバー
Covering up without being noticed
Here we go! 気取っちゃってさあ出番
Here we go! Putting on airs, it's showtime
爪を剥き出し
Baring my claws
非常なタカ稼業もどっか舐めるのなら
If you make light of this ruthless hawk business...
高が外れて容赦できなくなってヤバ炸裂
Things will go out of control and explode dangerously
本音かましようがねえぜすぐ鳴る
Can't help but speak my mind, it sounds out instantly
まじりけないハイブリッド揺らすこの世界
A pure hybrid shaking this world
咲いて果てど音に乗って明日へ
Blooming and withering, riding the sound to tomorrow
有無の有無まで頂いちゃお
I'll take everything, down to the very core
Here we go! 今夜だってバンバンバン
Here we go! Tonight too, bang bang bang
外さないクリア
A clear shot, no misses
いっそもっと目立ったら笑顔
If I were more conspicuous, a smile
今だに抜いた　とどめを呼ぶ
Calling the finishing blow I still struck
勢い寄せ待て　パンパパン
Gathering momentum, wait, Pan-pa-pan!
悟られず　カバー
Covering it without being noticed
耳元　陽気取ってさては
Cheerful in my ear, and then...
共に　脱出
Escaping together
TAKE OFF!
今日も秘密の　TAKE OFF!
Today too, a secret TAKE OFF!
ラストはこの曲です！
The last one is this song!
魔眼ウインク。
Magan Wink.
皆さん聴いてください、魔眼ウインク。
Everyone, please listen to: Magan Wink.
Soir... to be light...
Do you remember me? Haha!
シャルル目とメイクアップ
Charm eyes and make-up
アトラキトラがかったナイズめも　魔眼だわ
The attracted magnetized eyes too, are evil eyes
それはウィンク　ウィンク
That's a wink, wink
逃げてもずっとラック　アイムクレイジーなタイフーンの目　ウィンク
Even if you run, it's always luck, I'm a crazy typhoon's eye, wink
ショッキングな目がデカい　目に入れても痛くないくらい
Shocking, eyes are huge, so much so it doesn't hurt to put them in my eye
ララララ口走る　ディスリベンジャー
La-la-la-la blabbing out, Dis-revenger
慈しみの涙　どこに捨てた？
The tears of affection, where did you throw them?
怖がってんの？　ふん、あ、そう
Are you scared? Hmph, oh, I see.
Don't let me down
まだまだ
Not yet, not yet
安全じゃないから
Because it's not safe
健全じゃないから
Because it's not wholesome
それがなんだ　バクチだね
Whatever it is, it's a gamble
目には目を
An eye for an eye
ウィンク　せらららび　せきゅらら　ギブミーア　ウィンク
Wink, c'est la la vie, secular, give me a wink
せらららび　魔眼だわ
C'est la la vie, it's an evil eye
オー　アイアイアイ　ウォンチューで　バイバイバイ　アンスア
Oh, I-I-I, want you, bye-bye-bye, answer
目に戻らせる　マイアイアイ
Returning to my eye, my I-I
いいよ　目を瞑る半分ね
It's okay, closing half an eye
魔眼ウインク
Magan Wink
ほらごらん　またたく間に　アイアイアイキルユー
Look, in the blink of an eye, I-I-I kill you
ウィンク
Wink
後ろ指　指したいなら　お好きにどうぞ
If you want to point fingers, feel free
どうせ　振り返らぬ　肖像　残りたーい
Anyway, I want to remain as a portrait that doesn't look back
お待たせ　続々　おさらば　恨み買った
Thanks for waiting, one after another, farewell, I've earned your grudge
ベイベーな　特注のリメー
Baby-like custom-made reme
I'm coming back, I'm coming back, I'm coming back
メジャーじゃない　眼中にない
Not major, not even in my sight
そうさ　善良じゃないだろう
That's right, I'm not virtuous, am I?
最良じゃないだろう
Not the best, am I?
それがどうした　バクチだね
So what? It's a gamble
目には目を　歯には歯を
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth
ルイは何を呼ぶ
What does Lui call for?
せらららび　羽ばたきを
C'est la la vie, flapping wings
知るウィンク　目が離せない
Knowing the wink, I can't take my eyes off
完璧なウィンク
A perfect wink
もう　目が離せない　アイアイアイ
I can't take my eyes off you anymore, I-I-I
魔眼ウインク
Magan Wink
ほらごらん　またたく間に　アイアイアイ
Look, in the blink of an eye, I-I-I
アイキルユー
I kill you
ウィンク
Wink
重大発表
Major Announcement
Project "L"
鷹嶺ルイ 1st Album
Takane Lui 1st Album
ウインク　selalala　赤裸々メロディ　君へウインク
Wink, selalala, a candid melody, a wink for you
ウインク　selalala　山風が...
Wink, selalala, the mountain wind...
愛やいや i want you で bye bye answer...
Love or not, I want you, so a bye-bye answer...
...目にもの見せる My Eye Eye Eye, in flow 目をつむる
...I'll show you what's what, My Eye Eye Eye, in flow, I close my eyes
はい！ということで、重大告知させていただきました！
Yes! So, I've just made a major announcement!
重大告知は、なんと！
And that major announcement is...
鷹嶺ルイ 1st Album『Liberty』がリリース決定です！イエーイ！
Takane Lui's 1st Album 'Liberty' release has been confirmed! Yay!
あ、みんなね、拍手してくれてますね、ありがとうございます。
Oh, everyone's applauding. Thank you so much.
こちらね、鷹嶺ルイの1stアルバム『Liberty』、皆さん予想できていましたでしょうか？
This is Takane Lui's 1st album 'Liberty'. Did you all see this coming?
今回はですね、あのholoXの1曲はあったんですけど、それ以外は全曲、
This time, while there was that one holoX song,
鷹嶺ルイのオリジナル曲で構成させていただきました。
the rest are all Takane Lui's original songs.
『Liberty』は、21時からオフィシャルショップで販売開始になります。
'Liberty' will go on sale at the Official Shop starting at 21:00.
デジタルリリースはこの後24時から各音楽サイトで配信が開始されます。
The digital release will be available on music sites from 24:00 tonight.
『魔眼ウインク』と今日お披露目した新曲を含む全10曲のアルバムになっております。
It's a 10-track album, including 'Magan Wink' and the new song I performed today.
収録内容は、あ、しゅ、あはは！収録内容は、こちら！
The tracklist is... ah, tr- hahaha! The tracklist is right here!
『ひみつのおしごと』、先ほどやらせていただいた『ひみつのおしごと』に始まり、
Starting with 'Himitsu no Oshigoto', which I performed earlier,
カリ先輩とやった『ばかばっか』、『FIRST CRY』、『CHARISMA』、
'Baka Bakka' with Cali-senpai, 'FIRST CRY', 'CHARISMA',
『オーバード』、『Tori To ReTreaT』、『ホロホーク』...
'Overd', 'Tori To ReTreaT', 'HoloHawk'...
そして、あれ？『夢ができたの』『TSUBASA』、まだやってないなーっていう曲もありますが、
And then, huh? 'Yume ga Dekita no' and 'TSUBASA'... There are songs I haven't done yet,
この10曲が入ったアルバムになっております。
but those 10 tracks make up the album.
イラストはSOLANI先生、ロゴはsaku2先生に作っていただきました。
The illustration is by SOLANI-sensei, and the logo is by saku2-sensei.
購入特典として、MVから厳選したシーンのカットのフィルム風しおりを...
As a purchase bonus, a film-strip style bookmark featuring scenes from the MV...
ランダム封入させていただきます。
...will be included randomly.
シークレットもあるので全5種類の中から1枚封入させていただきます。
There's a secret one, so one out of 5 types will be included.
さらに、直筆サイン入りのアナザージャケットもついてきちゃいます。こちら！
Plus, it comes with a hand-signed another jacket! Here it is!
こちら、購入者全員に直筆サインで書いていただきますので...
I'll be hand-signing these for everyone who purchases one,
腕が大丈夫かって心配あるかもしれませんが、思いを込めて書いちゃうんでね、
so you might worry about my arm, but I'll put my heart into signing every one,
ぜひぜひ購入していただけたら嬉しいなと思います。よろしくお願いします。
so I'd be very happy if you'd buy it. Thank you!
注意事項ですが、今回のアルバムの到着時期がですね、
Just a heads up, the shipping date for this album...
誕生日グッズよりも早めに発送できる予定になっております。
...is expected to be earlier than the birthday goods.
早く欲しい方は、カートを誕生日グッズと分けて注文をしてください。
If you want it sooner, please order it separately from the birthday goods.
カートを一緒にしてしまうと、誕生日グッズと一緒に届くので注意してください。
If you put them in the same cart, they'll ship together with the birthday goods, so be careful.
そして、21時からは誕生日記念グッズ2024も発売開始されます。こちら！
Also, the 2024 Birthday Commemoration Goods go on sale from 21:00! Here they are!
タオル、缶バッジ、ぬいぐるみ、痛バッグの4種類でフルセットもございます。
There are 4 items: towel, badge, plushie, and ita-bag, plus a full set.
フルセットには箔押し複製サイン入りカードと特典ボイスがついてきます。
The full set includes a foil-stamped signature card and bonus voice.
数量限定版には特典カードに直筆メッセージを書いていっちゃいます。
For the limited edition, I'll be writing a handwritten message on the bonus card.
アルバムは直筆サイン、こちらは直筆メッセージになってますのでご注意ください。
The album is a signature, but this is a message, so please keep that in mind.
まだまだあります！21時5分からは『魔眼ウインク』のMVがプレミア公開します！
There's more! The 'Magan Wink' MV premieres at 21:05! Yay!
今回も、YMさんに作っていただきましたMVになっております。
This MV was also created by YM-san.
すごくかっこいい感じに仕上がっているので、ぜひ見てください。
It turned out really cool, so please go check it out.
ハッシュタグ『魔眼ウインク投稿チャレンジ』キャンペーンも開催中でございます。
The #MaganWinkPostingChallenge campaign is also ongoing.
6月30日までなので要チェックです。
It runs until June 30th, so be sure to check it out.
そして、ここからはコラボのお知らせです。告知が多くてすみません。
And now, for a collaboration announcement. Sorry for all the announcements.
なんと、DAMさんでコラボキャンペーンを実施することになりました！イエーイ！
Believe it or not, we're doing a collaboration campaign with DAM! Yay!
精密採点で...
With precision scoring...
...課題曲を歌いまして、
...by singing the challenge song,
参加者全員の累計得点が10万点に達しますと、
if the total score of all participants reaches 100,000 points,
限定メッセージ動画をプレゼントいたします！
we'll give away a limited message video!
え、参加してくださった方には、オリジナル壁紙プレゼント、
Also, participants will receive an original wallpaper,
さらに抽選で10名様にオリジナルステンレスボトルをプレゼント！
plus 10 lucky winners will get an original stainless steel bottle!
なんか下、私見えてるな？あはは！
I can see myself at the bottom... Haha!
え、プレゼント。ダムでたくさんみんな歌ってくれると嬉しいです！
Yes, prizes. I hope everyone sings a lot on DAM!
そんなダムさんにて『オーバード』の
And on DAM, for 'Overd',
本人映像が本日6月11日から順次、え、配信開始しています！
the music video is being released starting today, June 11th!
こちら！
Here it is!
はい、ミュージックビデオと一緒に『オーバード』が歌えるので、
Yes, you can sing 'Overd' along with the music video,
この機会に足を運んでみてください！
so please take this opportunity to go and check it out!
今回のコラボを記念して、渋谷の、えー、グリコビジョンなど
To commemorate this collaboration, at Shibuya's Glico Vision
複数箇所でですね、ビジョン放送が決定しました！
and several other locations, vision broadcasts have been confirmed!
すげー！
Amazing!
こちらね、7月頃から放映予定なので、
They're scheduled to broadcast around July,
詳細は、お待ちいただければなと思います。
so please wait for further details.
また詳細発表させていただきます。
I'll announce the details later.
まだまだ嬉しいお知らせがあります！あと、あと、あと、もうちょっとです！
There are still more happy announcements! Just, just, just a few more!
え、6月13日木曜日22時より放送のラジオ
On Thursday, June 13th, from 10:00 PM,
『SCHOOL OF LOCK!』に私、先生として初出演させていただきます！
I'll make my first appearance as a teacher on 'SCHOOL OF LOCK!'
はい、ということで、生徒のみなさんぜひぜひ聴いてください！
So, students, please be sure to listen in!
はい、嬉しいお知らせをたくさんさせていただきましたが、ここでですね、
I've shared many happy announcements, and now...
今日のこのライブを一緒に作ってくれた素敵なバンドメンバーのみなさんを
I'd like to introduce the wonderful band members
ご紹介させていただきたいと思います！
who helped create this live performance with me today!
バンドメンバーのみなさん、どうぞ！お待たせしました！え、長くてすみませんね！
Band members, please come in! Sorry for the wait! Sorry for the long wait!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
イエーイ、戻ってきてくれました！
Yay, they're back!
ということで、ちょっと紹介をしていきましょうかね。
So, let's go ahead and introduce them.
準備は大丈夫ですか？みなさん。
Is everyone ready?
みなさん大丈夫ですね。うん、って頷いてる。あはは！
Everyone's good. They're nodding 'yeah'. Haha!
ということで、バンドメンバーの紹介です！それでは...
So, here's the band introduction! First up...
ベース、Keiさん！
Bass, Kei-san!
ふー！かっこいい！かっこいいね、やっぱりベースって。低音でかっこいいよね！
Whoo! So cool! Bass is really cool, isn't it? That low sound is so cool!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
そして、キーボード、クワッチさん！
And, Keyboard, Kuwachi-san!
ふー！オシャレですね！ありがとう...やんちゃ。やんちゃですね！
Whoo! How stylish! Thank you... mischievous. How mischievous!
ありがとうございます！そして、ギター、カルロスさん！
Thank you! And, Guitar, Carlos-san!
くー！かっこいーぜ、ありがとうございます！
Kuu! That was cool, thank you very much!
やーかっこいいな！あはは！
Wow, so cool! Haha!
はい、そして、最後にバンドマスターで、
Yes, and finally, our Band Master,
ドラム...ドラムでバンドマスターもしてくださった、グーさん！
Drums... Guu-san, who also served as our Band Master on drums!
ふー！いやかっこいいですね！ありがとうございます！
Whoo! Man, that's cool! Thank you very much!
そしてですね、あの、このメンバーには、ちょっとあの、こういうね、
And also, well, among these members, for this, well...
3Dでは登場していないんですけれども、
though they haven't appeared in 3D,
え、裏にですね、マニピュレーター、パスタさんがいます！ありがとうございます！
in the back, we have our Manipulator, Pasta-san! Thank you!
あ、ぴゅろろろろろ。私がじゃあ効果音を。ぴゅろろろ。あ、手振ってくれてます！
Ah, pyu-ro-ro-ro-ro. I'll do the sound effects. Pyu-ro-ro. Oh, they're waving!
ありがとうございます！というメンバーでお送りさせていただきました！
Thank you very much! These are the members who performed today!
ということであとね、2曲歌わせていただくんですが、
So, I'll be singing two more songs, but...
21時15分からはメンバーシップ限定ライブも、このまま生バンドでお届けしたいと思います！
from 9:15 PM, we'll have a membership-exclusive live with this live band!
この機会にぜひメンバーシップに参加してみてください！
Please take this opportunity to join our membership!
ということで、え、まだやっていない2曲がありますね。
So, well, there are still two songs we haven't done yet.
次の曲はですね、『夢ができたの』という曲になるんですけれども、
The next song is called 'Yume ga Dekita no' (A Dream was Born),
これは私が、え、ホロライブに入る前、
and this is a song that was written for me,
ホロライブを見つけて、「あ、ホロライブに入りたいな」って思った、
capturing the feelings I had before joining Hololive,
え、その思いのままを書いていただいた、書き下ろしていただいた楽曲になります。
when I first found them and thought, "I want to join Hololive."
はい。聴いていただきたいんですが、その前に、
Yes. I'd like you to hear it, but before that,
水を飲みます。ちょっとすみません、水を飲ませてください。
I'm going to drink some water. Sorry, let me have some water.
ね、このままいったらエモいやんって思ったでしょう？
See, you thought it was going to be emotional just like that, right?
え、ちょっと水飲まないとやっていけなかったんで、水を飲ませていただきました！
Well, I couldn't keep going without some water, so I had some!
ということで。みなさん準備は大丈夫ですかね？
So. Is everyone ready?
ということでちょっと、え、ホロライブに
So, well, since I joined
入って私のね、たくさん夢が叶っていたんですけれども、
Hololive, many of my dreams have come true,
やっぱりホロライブにも目指したきっかけっていう思いは忘れたくないなと思いまして、
but I don't want to forget the feelings that first inspired me to aim for Hololive,
この曲を歌わせていただきます。聴いてください。
so I'm going to sing this song. Please listen.
夢ができたの
A Dream Was Born
そこは私が憧れた 星たちの世界
That was the world of stars I long for
両手いっぱいの愛を持って 灯りにしてる
With my hands full of love, I make it a light
間違い事だけ 染めるような灯りに
To a light that seems to dye only mistakes
夢ができたの この星の夜は 暗いでしょう
I have a dream, the night of this star is dark, isn't it?
どんな時でも とびきり優しい 灯火になりたいの
No matter when, I want to become an exceptionally gentle guiding light
夕暮れに口をこぼして泣いた 昨日の私は
My yesterday self, who complained and cried at dusk
ネガティブ事 丸めて捨てた 生まれ変わったの
Rolled up and threw away all the negativity, I was reborn
高い壁があるのなら 当たって砕けちゃえ
If there's a high wall, I'll just go for broke and crash into it
ひとりきりでは この星の夜は 暗いでしょう
All alone, the night of this star is dark, isn't it?
君の明日を 照らし出すような 灯火になりたいの
I want to become a light that illuminates your tomorrow
夢ができたの この星の夜は 暗いでしょう
I have a dream, the night of this star is dark, isn't it?
どんな時でも とびきり優しい 灯火になりたいの
No matter when, I want to become an exceptionally gentle guiding light
はいということで 夢ができたの 歌わせていただきました。
And so, I just sang "A Dream Was Born."
またね アルバムの詳細だったりとか 楽曲のこだわりについては 振り返り配信だったりとかで お話しさせていただければなと思います。
As for the album details and the specifics of the songs, I hope to talk about those in a recap stream later on.
そして え 次が本当に最後の曲になります。
And now, the next one will truly be the final song.
今日は本当に皆さん 集まってくれて え 応援してくれて ありがとうございました。
Thank you all so much for gathering here and supporting me today.
え ちょっとね 喉が不完全ではあるので
My throat isn't in perfect condition right now,
またね なんか リベンジしたいな なんて ははは
so I'd like to try this again sometime. Hahaha.
リベンジさせていただきたいなと 思います。
I'd love to take another shot at it.
はい すごい生バンドライブ え 初のわたくしねの 試みだったんですが すごく楽しかったです。
This was my first attempt at a live band concert, and it was so much fun.
こうやってね 夢を叶えていけるのは え ルイ友さんはじめ え こうやってね ホロライブをこう盛り上げてくださる ホロリスの皆さん
Being able to fulfill my dreams like this is thanks to my Lui-tomo, and the Hololive fans who keep things so lively.
そしてホロライブのメンバー そして運営さんのおかげだと思っているので 本当に皆さん ありがとうございました。
And also the Hololive members and staff. Thank you all so much.
これからも 鷹嶺ルイ 頑張っていきたいと思いますので 皆さん 応援ぜひぜひ よろしくお願いします。
I'll continue to do my best as Takane Lui, so I'd appreciate your continued support.
夢は ソロライブ 頑張って叶えるぞー！
My dream is a solo concert! I'll do my best to make it happen!
ということで ちょっとお水を飲んで
On that note, let me take a quick sip of water...
歌わせていただきます。
...before I sing for you.
え 最後の曲は 私が作詞に参加させていただきました。
For this final song, I also participated in writing the lyrics.
え ルイ友さんへの 感謝の気持ちを込めて 歌いたいと思います。
I'll sing it with all my gratitude for my Lui-tomo.
聞いてください 翼。
Please listen: "Tsubasa."
TSUBASA
...ないで 私がいつもついてるよ
...don't cry, I'll always be with you.
辛いのを 隠しがちな君
You, who tends to hide your pain,
放っておけないよ
I can't just leave you alone.
大丈夫 泣かないで
It's okay, please don't cry.
でも無理に笑わないで
But don't force a smile, either.
ゆっくり 空見上げてよ
Look up at the sky slowly,
似た者同士で
as we're two of a kind.
翼を傷めた君に
To you, whose wings are hurt,